[{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975289487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":104703,"timeElapsed":371036},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975317386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":27887,"timeElapsed":398936},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975339161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":21768,"timeElapsed":420712},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975356159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":16989,"timeElapsed":437710},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975389419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":33252,"timeElapsed":470970},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975436780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":47354,"timeElapsed":518331},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975444498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7711,"timeElapsed":526049},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975453283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":8778,"timeElapsed":534833},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975461626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8333,"timeElapsed":543176},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975484057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":20743,"timeElapsed":565608},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975493325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":9262,"timeElapsed":574875},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975502775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":9446,"timeElapsed":584326},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975509726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6943,"timeElapsed":591277},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975516413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6682,"timeElapsed":597963},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975522769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6349,"timeElapsed":604319},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975529639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6861,"timeElapsed":611190},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975536566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6921,"timeElapsed":618116},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975544440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":7869,"timeElapsed":625991},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975571573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":25470,"timeElapsed":653124},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975580609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9028,"timeElapsed":662159},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975592388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":11771,"timeElapsed":673939},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975597508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5114,"timeElapsed":679059},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975602544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5030,"timeElapsed":684095},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975606533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3984,"timeElapsed":688084},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975611823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":5280,"timeElapsed":693373},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975616708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4879,"timeElapsed":698259},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975620210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3496,"timeElapsed":701761},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975668805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":46200,"timeElapsed":750355},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975674907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":6096,"timeElapsed":756458},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975682962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":8049,"timeElapsed":764513},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975688380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5412,"timeElapsed":769931},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975693828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5442,"timeElapsed":775379},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975697996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4162,"timeElapsed":779547},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975703846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5845,"timeElapsed":785397},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975710309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6458,"timeElapsed":791860},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975729173,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":18857,"timeElapsed":810723},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975738532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":9354,"timeElapsed":820083},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975749413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":8253,"timeElapsed":830963},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975756093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":6673,"timeElapsed":837643},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975759959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3860,"timeElapsed":841509},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975762783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2816,"timeElapsed":844333},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975765655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2867,"timeElapsed":847206},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975768270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2608,"timeElapsed":849819},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975773566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5291,"timeElapsed":855117},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975776341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2768,"timeElapsed":857892},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975780886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4536,"timeElapsed":862436},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975804271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":21625,"timeElapsed":885822},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975808215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3938,"timeElapsed":889766},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975810587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2364,"timeElapsed":892138},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975812997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2404,"timeElapsed":894547},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975815803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2799,"timeElapsed":897354},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975818956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":900507},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975822735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3770,"timeElapsed":904285},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975825971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":907522},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975828605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2629,"timeElapsed":910156},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975841136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":10261,"timeElapsed":922687},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975844554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3413,"timeElapsed":926105},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975847383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2823,"timeElapsed":928933},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975850693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3303,"timeElapsed":932243},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975854584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3885,"timeElapsed":936135},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975857572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2979,"timeElapsed":939123},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975862193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4615,"timeElapsed":943743},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975865763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3566,"timeElapsed":947314},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975869981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4210,"timeElapsed":951531},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975884697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":13016,"timeElapsed":966247},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975892169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":7464,"timeElapsed":973719},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975901569,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9394,"timeElapsed":983120},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975907577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6001,"timeElapsed":989127},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975912102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4520,"timeElapsed":993653},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975915573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3466,"timeElapsed":997124},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975919735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4157,"timeElapsed":1001286},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975924217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4474,"timeElapsed":1005768},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975927756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3534,"timeElapsed":1009306},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975931345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3585,"timeElapsed":1012896},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975957493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":23907,"timeElapsed":1039044},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975964152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6651,"timeElapsed":1045702},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975968111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3954,"timeElapsed":1049662},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975971034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2915,"timeElapsed":1052585},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975974180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3141,"timeElapsed":1055731},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975977389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3202,"timeElapsed":1058940},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975981953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4560,"timeElapsed":1063504},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975989410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":7451,"timeElapsed":1070961},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975992588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":1074139},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976004001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9713,"timeElapsed":1085551},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976007710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3704,"timeElapsed":1089260},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976011344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3628,"timeElapsed":1092895},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976016685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5332,"timeElapsed":1098236},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976024093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":7404,"timeElapsed":1105644},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976030334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6234,"timeElapsed":1111885},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976033690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":1115241},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976036945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3250,"timeElapsed":1118495},{"subjectID":"43x4y7fcvj","prolificID":"6683df32c21487204a0b9905","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d782c75f8063f90a1b8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976040472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3520,"timeElapsed":1122023}]